Because we're committing items 4 through 8 for the consent agenda.
If you'll take a quick look at those.
And if they're on no questions, we'll entertain a motion.
Mayor, did you ask me to send you a chance to look at them?
No use on them.
I have not reviewed them specifically now.
You want to do one thing?
You want to see it in the eye.
So this is the last stop.
Do you have a little fruit?
Okay.
And you might as well prove it to me.
Second.
Go call please.
Johnson.
Forster.
All right.
Question.
Louis.
I shall ask.
I.
And by the way, Amanda, is it a question?
This is so she should apologize to me.
Okay.
I don't know how to take some partnership contract for the South End Honors Plaza.
I'd like to speak just a couple minutes on this.
We can analyze that.
She talked about the structure.
I'm not about building somehow.
It wants to be always pleasant.
Especially the illness that we're in.
But we have the illness.
We come today.
We have a potential statute.
And that error.
I'm a reminder that the funds that would be needed to be funds that are not needed for the
bond issue.
The point six five to six cents.
Which goes to you to run for to stay.
And we have laid out the plan and scheduled for this project.
The hope is that by doing this project, we have a lot of standing up.
We have a lot of time.
So these findings that we have right now.
We need to think about it.
We've got a lot of work to say.
It's not like that.
And it doesn't come off.
We'll have to bring the comparative fee on the square,
so that it else gets her foyer and seedlons sketch.
And the whole goal here is to have a statute
of vice.
We know it by the September.
Can't, also, definitely, have advice to recommend them.
If you've had a virtue to see it, you might
So it's what's actually, and by the way there's at least one class of 75 number that is already going to be just checked for it.
It's going to be two letters that are printed in pretty sick of it.
So what we're going to have tonight is improving the complex and after that.
We have a study session, they have a group of some kind of March, and we would be bringing to you the question.
We have a group of data and we have a construction company.
So they're on that.
Then we have a draft.
I think we'll have a week of course, a total of those projects.
But I'll see if it's just another opportunity to give you any questions.
The problem is that far, right?
Okay.
And the cost of this contract was included in the dollars that we discussed at the study session.
And that was an opportunity to do all that.
That we hope as an upper end instrument.
We hope that we can send you an opportunity to help us.
Some of you find support and prepare cost.
And that's what we have one of the biggest factors and things.
And especially factory and what contract you might have for the profit or something like that.
So we have a couple of people that we would like to do.
We would want to name that for five.
That would be the answer.
Any questions for Dean?
So do we have a motion to approve the contract with Architects and Partnership?
I'll make the motion.
And a second.
That's a roll call please.
Listen.
Johnson.
Forster.
Lewis.
No.
Schultz.
Adam 10.
Ordinance 2018.
There I show a form and in.
Nice place is what we just talked about, right?
And then okay.
So it's the same issue as we had in the issue.
I'm meeting with the skirmers there and the rounding of two places instead of four.
If there are another question that I entertain the motion to approve.
And a second.
Second.
Roll call please.
Johnson.
Forster.
Western.
Lewis.
I.
Schultz.
Thank you.
We do not need to worry about this.
Good.
Thank you.
Adam 11 is not mine.
The moon is not an issue in the table.
Downers are coming to the library board or turn.
Which will expire.
The new term would expire.
Two twenty of twenty one.
So I'll put that before you for consideration.
You need a motion.
Yes.
I'll make a motion.
I'll second it.
Roll call.
Western.
Lewis.
Forster.
Johnson.
I.
And I.
And 12 similarly.
More among think about this.
From one point of view.
According to DO.
Before.
So, one second.
And so I think we are going to start.
Brown, we all went.
On the stop.
We're going to have this meeting last week and Dean was going to present this and say here's what we're planning on saying just to make sure everybody is on the same page of course our meeting
I got canceled, we went ahead, Dean Spow, Larry Bork, the plaintiff's attorney, Spow,
several travel weapons in Spow, I spoke briefly at the very end, several residents got
up in Spow, and told their stories, I was going to have more residents there, but the ones
that were there, you know, really had some, some heart-wrenching stories, and so I, I, and she spoke
in Tulsa, or Langley, Langley, she says she could stand it, she had also could stand, she couldn't stand
the more, Spowby would say, so you have the statement as part of your packet, it's already
been shared with folk, I don't know, any any questions, what did I do like to say about the
packet, but what is there, there are some elements in there that we actually call them in
Europe, and I want to be a reasonable item to say that, you know, later on, we were not always
against Europe yet, there were a lot of things that could have that could potentially help
on them, there are a lot of things that they have started doing when we did that, and so
I managed to approach that thing, we think it's so fun, yeah, that's just the top of your steps,
there are a lot of other things that need to be done, but what we've really implemented are a number
of things that really are, for example, in Sloan Routen, so a flood ran across that, for example, there's
never really been down on this entire watershed, in fact, I don't know if I'm sure it's just
bad, that there is a water resources over there that's going to be going to be going to be going to
be going to be on about 100 grand for the soil, but so originally, yeah, I should be 96, and it's just
the end of the road, and I changed the worrying to include both the elk and the spring road at our
request, and that's now happening. We are wanting to go for funding for both, say I probably want to
be firing at you, but you're going to be going to be going to be going to be going to be going to
and also the less people who are potentially raised those properties, also acquiring these
and such lines of life, but that's a major major issue, and then also we have a lot of tribal properties,
now, and a lot of the cultural resources, and you know, there's still a lot of the sites to be
going to preserve those, and we've got a very important part of this project, and while it doesn't
affect us correctly, you'll see a statement that the tribal history of mine is, but so we need to
present and protect that as well, but there are a lot of different moving parts, and a lot of these parts are
not only part of the third part since we're going to be involved in four of this years, we're going to be
going to be involved in Congress, and it's a kind of a daunting process. This is a five-week program
we're going to be going to be going to be going to talk about Congress.
still be final by after we launched our key.
And I worry that anybody has a problem
to a filmist who forms like this out,
or then had access to computers,
something like that.
Our library staff is there,
and they can help them out a lot.
So the major major project that we did underplay,
there will be additional public hearings.
I think that Dr. Bonsik will be coming back.
And I think that, I think that
I would like to put a master wants that this is the whole series.
When I asked a lot of artists, you could share your ideas,
you could share your ideas.
A lot of producing new things.
You could put that in the rest of the years.
This is a process that has smart album set.
It's a photo of the paper.
It also gives me a lot of wood.
It's a kind of a spark.
This is what we need to do.
A lot of other factors.
Spectacles.
We have a lot of people on our side.
A lot of people that are working out a lot of wood.
And that kind of leads a little bit into item 14,
which is capital ventures, government relations
claimed for February.
You should have in your package, Stuart,
report from his activities for the last several weeks.
Thank you.
Certainly, I've been very active being
and I've been on several conference calls with him
and the other attorneys that are representing us.
And in spite of the fact that he had the flu
and was hospitalized for a couple of weeks,
he certainly done a lot of good work for us this month.
So that's kind of the update again,
a written report is in your packet.
And if there's anything in there that doesn't make sense to you,
because he wrote it from the point of view
that he and I have been in those conversations
and I'm going to ask him next time to elaborate a little bit more.
But the idea there won't be happy to flesh out any questions
you might have.
So item 14 is capital ventures claim in 3,000.
Do we have emotion?
Right emotions.
Do you approve?
Two per per per.
We have a second.
So I get a local case.
Fourster.
All right.
Less than Lewis.
I'm Johnson.
Shult.
Hi.
Item 15 staff reports are in your packet
and they're still available if you have questions.
Excuse me.
Item 16 mayor and council community announcements
and the announcements.
No more.
Item 17 City Manager Communications.
I have obviously very short.
I just want to indicate that I sent an email to you
and also we're putting up other information that we're now in our code
that we need to have a process by which we're getting ready
next month for our community.
And what we do is to have people with an article
that we've decided that we're still signing a few other copies.
But at this point, we're going off on side patients to tell them we have to be putting that kind of stuff that we can actually tell them to take care of your problems.
We did it last year and it did work really well to help them work this year.
So if you have any issues that kind of are laid about people and the process will be in their proper condition, that when we work with those people, we're going to be telling them that a few weeks,
we will actually take care of them to take care of them to take care of them and help them get a lot of people to clean up their problems.
Any year, I think we see more and more stuff that we're holding on to do for understanding what we're planning to do.
I think it's an excellent compromise approach.
So I think it's a good idea. Anything else?
Okay.
I had a main team was executive session pursuant to 25 OS 307 B1 for the purposes of discussing the employment hiring appointment promotion devotions.
Disaffointing your resignation of any individual salary to public also employee to where in Georgia and Roy.
It's been a year and a phone.
You have something you'd like to add.
No, I don't need anything on this.
Okay.
I'm not talking about thinning litigation.
So we don't want you to go into executive session.
What are you doing there?
Okay.
Let's keep it that way.
Second.
We'll fall, please.
Johnson, Weston.